<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>anime convention &#8211; Mystery Club Comic</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/tag/anime-convention/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/blog/</link>
	<description>Story and Art by Amy Tucker</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 15:50:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.18</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Dekko Launch Party</title>
		<link>/blog/2017/06/26/dekko-launch-party/</link>
		<comments>/blog/2017/06/26/dekko-launch-party/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 14:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[amyt]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[conventions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amy tucker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anime convention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coffee=garbage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comic art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[convention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dekko]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dekko characters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dekko comics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[myster club festival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mystery club]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mystery club invisible ink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mystery club meet miss rock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[mystery club the spy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rai-con]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rossie stone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tea #1]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/?p=46</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Okay my last post was stupid but in that post I said the next one would be serious and I&#8217;m sticking to it!!! Right, in this post I want to talk a bit about Dekko Comics and their launch party and how I am involved with the company. So Dekko Comics is a comic book aimed &#8230; <a href="/blog/2017/06/26/dekko-launch-party/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Dekko Launch Party</span> <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-full wp-image-47 aligncenter" src="/blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/launch-party.jpg" alt="" width="501" height="708" srcset="/blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/launch-party.jpg 501w, /blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/launch-party-212x300.jpg 212w" sizes="(max-width: 501px) 100vw, 501px" />Okay my last post was stupid but in that post I said the next one would be serious and I&#8217;m sticking to it!!!</p>
<p>Right, in this post I want to talk a bit about <strong>Dekko Comics </strong>and their launch party and how I am involved with the company. So <strong>Dekko</strong> Comics is a comic book aimed at children as an alternative way to help them learn. The creator of <strong>Dekko</strong> is a man called <strong>Rossie Stone.</strong></p>
<p>Alright now that you know what <strong>Dekko</strong> is, I will start from the beginning and explain how I met <strong>Rossie. </strong>A few months ago I was at spring <strong>Rai-con,  </strong>I had a stall and I was selling my comic book <strong>Mystery Club, </strong>Rossie was also at <strong>Rai-con</strong>, to be honest I&#8217;m not sure is he was selling his book there or not (I can&#8217;t remember). Anyway, at one point during the convention I was away, ( probably eating&#8230;eating marshmallows&#8230;. WHAT?!! THEY WERE SELLING GOURMET MARSHMALLOWS <strong>HOW WAS I MEANT TO RESIST?!!!! </strong>) And my mum was keeping an eye on my stall &#8217;cause I do not have employees&#8230;</p>
<p>So when my mum was watching my stall I think <strong>Rossie</strong> came up to the stall and said he would come back later and buy my comic. Later on when I came back my mum told me but we didn&#8217;t actually think he would be back, but he was!</p>
<p>He bought all 4 of my books (I only had 4 books out at the time) <strong>Mystery Club Festival, Mystery Club Invisible Ink, Mystery club The Spy</strong> and <strong>Mystery Club Meet Miss ROCK! </strong>I think he gave me his business card and I happened to have forgot to bring any business cards so I just gave him my email address&#8230;..</p>
<p>A few weeks later we meet up for coffee, well I had tea &#8217;cause tea&#8217;s better, AM I RIGHT?!! We spoke about my comic and how I got started which is a subject I may want to speak about in another post. What I didn&#8217;t exactly realise though was that this was a sort of job interview! At the end he asked me if I would like to possibly work for<strong> Dekko.</strong></p>
<p>Before working for <strong>Dekko</strong> there are 3 stages, the 1st is copying pictures of <strong>Dekko </strong>characters, the 2nd is coming up with poses for the characters and drawing that and the 3rd is drawing some <strong>Dekko</strong> comic strips. Right now I am actually still on the 1st step but I am close to moving on to step 2 so I am not officially working for them now but hopefully I soon will be!</p>
<p>As I said, I am not officially working for them at the moment, but I was still invited  to the launch party for their 3rd volume and was given a stall to sell my books at!! It was a very fun night and I also met some of the other <strong>Dekko</strong> artists, listened to some very wonderful, inspirational talks, and sold out all my comics!!!</p>
<p>There should hopefully be some videos and photos from the night on <strong>Dekkos</strong> Facebook soon if you are interested so hopefully you can check that out!!</p>
<p><strong>Phew!</strong> That was a lot of writing! <em>Alrighty~ </em> see ya in ma next post (hopefully&#8230;)</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Amy</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/2017/06/26/dekko-launch-party/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bad hair!</title>
		<link>/blog/2017/06/25/bad-hair/</link>
		<comments>/blog/2017/06/25/bad-hair/#respond</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 22:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[amyt]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[conventions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[amy tucker]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[anime convention]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artists]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bad hair]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comic authors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[comics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rai-con]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog/?p=30</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Right, okay! I know this is the stupidest blog post possible to post but ya know what, this is my stupid blog and it can be as stupid as stupidly possible so let&#8217;s get on with the stupidity! So yeah, you know when you look up your name&#8230;(you do that don&#8217;t you?! I know you &#8230; <a href="/blog/2017/06/25/bad-hair/" class="more-link">Continue reading <span class="screen-reader-text">Bad hair!</span> <span class="meta-nav">&#8594;</span></a>]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img class="size-medium wp-image-31 alignnone" src="/blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/bad-hair-212x300.jpg" alt="" width="212" height="300" srcset="/blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/bad-hair-212x300.jpg 212w, /blog/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/bad-hair.jpg 501w" sizes="(max-width: 212px) 100vw, 212px" /></p>
<p>Right, okay! I know this is the stupidest blog post possible to post but ya know what, this is my stupid blog and it can be as stupid as stupidly possible so let&#8217;s get on with the stupidity!</p>
<p>So yeah, you know when you look up your name&#8230;(you do that don&#8217;t you?! I know you do it , IT CAN&#8217;T JUST BE ME!!! Can it&#8230;?)</p>
<p>Anyway when you look up your name you do <strong>not </strong>want to find a picture like this! <strong>THIS IS WHAT A CONVENTION DOES TO YOU, CHILDREN!!!</strong> THIS IS WHAT IT DOES&#8230;!</p>
<p>P.s. This was taken at Rai-con, it was getting late, I was having to pose for pictures, some kind of weird animal just had to chose my head to crawl on to to die but despite that it was <strong>so</strong> enjoyable!</p>
<p>I met many other comic book artists and writers and I also met Rossie Stone who has his own business called <strong>Dekko comics</strong> (I might speak more about that in another post) anyway if you have wrote a comic or made artwork or something similar, seriously, try and get a stall at a convention or even just go to a convention! You will meet so many people who can help you there!</p>
<p>Right, I think that&#8217;s enough rambling now&#8230;see ya in my next post! (hopefully&#8230;?)</p>
<p>Amy</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>/blog/2017/06/25/bad-hair/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
